var questionBank =[
	{
		question: 'What does the Dude drink?',
		options: ['Jack&Coke', 'White Russion', '7&7', 'Martini'],
		answer: options.1
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the name of Uli + the Nihlists band?',
		options: ['Autobahn', 'Blitz Kreig', 'The Berlin 8', 'Sauerkraut Soup'],
		answer: options.0		
	},
	{
		question: 'What kind of rug really tied the Dude’s room together?',
		options: ['Modern', 'Persian', 'White', 'Oriental'],
		answer: options.3		
	},
	{
		question: 'What’s the only form of ID the Dude carries on him?',
		options: ['Driving License', "Ralph's Card", 'Social Secutiry Card', 'School ID'],
		answer: options.1		
	},
	{
		question: ' Who directed the Big Lebowski?',
		options: ['The Cohen Brothers', "Danny DeVito", 'John Hughes', 'John Landis'],
		answer: options.0		
	},
	{
		question: 'Do you ever see the Dude bowl?',
		options: ['Yes', 'No'],
		answer: options.1		
	},
	{
		question: 'The Dude was a roadie for which band?',
		options: ["Jane's Addiction", 'Metallica', "The Grateful Dead", 'Ozzy Osbourne'],
		answer: options.1		
	},
	{
		question: 'How long did Jesus spend in Chino?',
		options: ["1 Year", '1 Month', "6 Years", '6 Months'],
		answer: options.3		
	},
	{
		question: 'Which band does the Dude “f^%*ing hate”?',
		options: ["Creedance Clearwater Revival", 'The Beach Boys', "The Eagles", 'Pink Floyd'],
		answer: options.2		
	},
	{
		question: 'Does the Dude Abide?',
		options: ['Yes', 'No', 'Maybe'],
		answer: options.0		
	}
]
